{"data":[{"question":"Veronica died in the hospital. She _________ if the doctor ___ on her one hour earlier.","a":"could be saved, had operated","b":"might be saved, operated","c":"had been saved, was operated","d":"could have been saved, had operated","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 3:  used to talk about things that didn't happened in the past and the consequence if they had happened\n+ Form: if + Past Perfect, would + have + Past Participle","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"___ the people would be leading a respected life.","a":"Had Mainland China been democratized","b":"Had Mainland China not been democratized","c":"Had not Mainland China been democratized","d":"If Mainland China hadn't democratized","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 2 and 3: used to talk about things that didn't happened in the past which result in consequence at present \n+ Form: if + Past Perfect, would + Verb \n- Sometimes conditional forms are inverted as a means of sounding more formal. In this case, the conditional 'if' is dropped and the inverted forms takes the place of the 'if clause' \n- Inversion clause: auxiliary + subject + main verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"It is required that the preparation ___ right now.","a":"should start","b":"would start","c":"should be started","d":"would be started","answer":"3","explain":"\n- The Subjunctive is used to emphasize urgency or importance. It is used after certain expressions: \n - S+ advise \/ask\/to command\/demand\/desire\/insist\/propose\/recommend\/request\/suggest\/ urge (that) + S + (would) Infinitive ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Now I wish I _________ him yesterday.","a":"didn't met","b":"don't meet","c":"hadn't met","d":"haven't met","answer":"3","explain":"\n- A wish about the past: Wish clause,had PP\/ should, could have PP","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Our boss ___ to stay in Hong Kong for one more week, but he changed his mind.","a":"had hoped","b":"hoped","c":"would hope","d":"was hoping","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Past Perfect: [had + past participle] \n- Past perfect: The Past Perfect expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"I was ill that day, otherwise I ___ the football match.","a":"had taken part in","b":"would take part in","c":"would have taken part in","d":"took part in","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Would have PP: used when talking about something that did not happen, or a situation that cannot exist ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"The child talks to us as if he ___ a grown-up.","a":"will be","b":"is","c":"were","d":"had been","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Clauses that start with as if\/as though express unreality, improbability or doubt if they are followed by an unreal tense \n- The simple past tense  is used if we talk about an unreal situation in the present","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"You ___ to the meeting this morning. What was the reason for your absence?","a":"would have come","b":"should have come","c":"had come","d":"came","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Should have PP: used to say what would have been right or sensible, but was not done ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Kelly insisted that she ___ ill of her manager behind him, but he didn't believe her.","a":"shouldn't speak","b":"hadn't spoken","c":"not speak","d":"wouldn't speak","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Past perfect: The Past Perfect expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past (insisted)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Your boss's silence suggested that he _________ to your project.","a":"hadn't agreed","b":"didn't agree","c":"shouldn't agree","d":"wouldn't agree","answer":"2","explain":"- We use the past tense","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"}]}